brandstack.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy | BrandCrowd

_By using the site you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this policy._

BrandCrowd is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy tells you about usage of our site, as well as, use and disclosure of personal information. The terms of this policy apply to all personal and business information collected by BrandCrowd on the BrandCrowd.com and other BrandCrowd related procedures.

This site is operated by DesignCrowd Pty Ltd trading as BrandCrowd. For information protection purposes, BrandCrowd is the controller and, unless otherwise noted, is also the processor of the personal information. Information collected may be retained as long as it is reasonably required for the purposes it was collected.

**Consent to Collection of Your Personal Information**

When you visit this site, certain kinds of non-personal information, such as the website that referred you to us, your IP address, browser type and language, and access times, may be collected automatically as part of the site's operation. We also may collect navigational information, including information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions taken in connection with the site. Demographic information may also be collected and may be linked to your personal information.

We only collect personal information about you after you have provided us with your consent to collect that specific information. By voluntarily providing this information to us, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as set out in this privacy policy.

Personal information includes:

At some points, BrandCrowd collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. BrandCrowd may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. BrandCrowd may collect financial information to purchase and sell on BrandCrowd.com including credit card number and billing address, as well as, banking and other financial information required to compensate you.

BrandCrowd may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken within BrandCrowd.com. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.

Certain BrandCrowd services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both companies may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services.

**Use of Your Personal Information**

BrandCrowd collects and uses your personal information to:

1\. create and manage your membership account;

2\. process your transactions;

3\. provide customer service;

4\. perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies;

5\. to display content that is customized to your interests and preferences;

6\. to run contests, select entrants, and choose prize winners;

7\. to run interactive areas;

8\. to compensate you if you are a seller;

9\. to identify your uploaded content as your content if you are a seller; and,

10\. to communicate with you about your transactions, new products and services. We may send transaction-related communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, and purchase confirmations. We may also send you surveys or marketing communications to inform you of new products or services or other information or offers that may be of interest. If you do not wish to receive surveys or marketing communications, you may adjust your preferences in the “My Account” section or follow the "unsubscribe" instructions included within each email communication. If you choose not to receive marketing communications, you will continue to receive transactional or account communications.

Personal information collected by BrandCrowd may be stored and processed in any country in which BrandCrowd is used and by providing us with your personal information and using our sites or services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. If you would like to exercise any of your personal information protection rights (including the right to have your personal information deleted), please contact us by email at dataprotection@designcrowd.com.

**Disclosing Your Personal Information**

Except as set out in this privacy policy, BrandCrowd does not disclose or sell your personal information to any third-parties.

We may disclose your personal information to third-party service providers who perform services on our behalf such as to handle the processing of payments, to provide data storage, to host websites, to fulfill orders, to assist in marketing, to conduct audits, etc. Those third-party service providers (i) shall be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to provide the service, (ii) must protect personal information to the same extent as BrandCrowd, and (iii) shall be prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

Personal information disclosed BrandCrowd may be available to the United States government or its agencies under a lawful order made in a court of competent jurisdiction in the US.

If you have entered into an BrandCowd contest, we or a contest sponsor may publish your name and city of residence. Information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, or sale of the company and/or its assets, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. We will notify you of such an occurrence as described in the "Changes to This Privacy Policy" section below. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required or permitted to do so by law.

**Accessing Your Personal Information**

If you would like to review or revise information that you previously provided to us, you may access and change your personal information in the "My Account" section of the site. You may also contact Customer Service by email at support@brandcrowd.com for assistance.

**Personal Information Preferences**

BrandCrowd respects your right to make choices about the use and disclosure of your personal information. If at any time you decide that you do not want to receive surveys or marketing communications from us, please let us know by: (1) checking or unchecking the appropriate box on your online registration form when you sign up or the in "My Account" page of the website once you are a member; (2) contacting Customer Service by email at support@brandcrowd.com.

If you choose not to receive marketing communications, please be advised that you will continue to receive transactional or account communications (e.g., confirmation emails and account balance statements).

**Use of Cookies and Other Technologies**

BrandCrowd uses "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive. Cookies contain information, including personal information, that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit, your registration information, session identification number and your navigational history and preferences.

Cookies offer you many conveniences. They allow us to identify registered users when they return to the site so that they can access online portfolios, “favorites” and view their transaction history. Cookies also save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information.

In some cases, our third-party service providers may use cookies on our sites. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by BrandCrowd only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies but you will be able to perform basic navigation through the site.

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies, including single-pixel gifs (also known as web beacons) on our websites and in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters. These tiny electronic images assist us in determining how many users have visited certain pages or opened messages or newsletters. We do not use these images to collect personal information.

**Security of Your Personal Information**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to help protect your personal information including without limitation:

1\. limiting access to your personal information to those of our employees who require it to provide services to you;

2\. requiring employees to sign confidentiality agreements to protect customer and other confidential information;

3\. ensuring that third-party service providers sign confidentiality agreements to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and not to use it for any unauthorized purposes;

encrypting credit card information on our order forms using secure socket layer (SSL) technology; and

4\. storing your personal information in secure computer systems which protect it from unauthorized access or use.

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If a password is used to protect your account and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential.

**Discussion Forums & Other Interactive Services**

Our sites may include discussion forums or other interactive areas or services, including blogs, chat rooms, bulletin boards, message boards, online hosting or storage services, or other areas or services in which you or third parties create, post or store any content, messages, comments, materials or other items on the sites ("Interactive Areas"). If you use an Interactive Area, you should be aware that these areas are open to the public and any personal information you post or provide at registration may be viewable by others. We are not responsible for personal information you submit in connection with the Interactive Areas, nor are we responsible for how others might use that information, including sending you unsolicited messages. Interactive Area postings may be retained indefinitely. If at any time you would like to remove a posting, please email us at support@brandcrowd.com. Keep in mind that removal of a posting from an Interactive Area does not mean that the posting will be deleted from our systems.

**Email Referrals**

If you choose to use our email referral services to tell a friend about our products or services we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will use that information to send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site and review the product or service you have selected. We may use a third-party provider to administer this function, but any such third-party provider may only use the information submitted to facilitate this one-time email.

**Children**

We do not intend to solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18 without parental consent. If you are under 18, you shall not use or enter information on this site, including without limitation, any Interactive Areas of the site without parental consent. Please contact Customer Services by email at support@brandcrowd.com to obtain the necessary parental consent forms.

**Links**

We may link to websites, including third-party content providers, that have different privacy policies and practices from those disclosed here. We assume no responsibility for the policies or practices of such linked sites and encourage you to become acquainted with them prior to use.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. If there are material changes to this statement or in how BrandCrowd will use your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes here or on our home page, or by sending you an email. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit one of our sites.

**Contact Information**

BrandCrowd welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that we have not adhered to this Statement, please contact us e-mail.
